Guide to Rice University Vice President of Finance and Administration office records, 1938-2010 UA 140
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series IV: Neill Binford Finance and Administration, 1983 - 2004
  - President's Office: General Correspondence, 1992 - 2003 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - President's Office: Miscellaneous, 1996 - 1997 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - President's Office: O'Connor House, 1986 - 2003 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - President's Office: Parking - Binford/Cannady, 2002 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - President's Office: Parking - Budget Issues, 2002 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - President's Office: Parking Committee, 2003 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - President's Office: Parking Complaints, 2002 - 2003 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - President's Office: Parking - Other Issues, 2001 - 2004 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - President's Office: Parking - Shepherd School, 2002 - 2003 (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - President's Office: Parking - Spouse/Partner Issue, 2003 (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - President's Office: Parking - Students, 2002 (Box 93, Folder 16)
  - President's Office: Parking Validations, 2002 (Box 93, Folder 17)
  - President's Office: Presdient - Elect Malcolm Gillis, 1993 - 1994 (Box 93, Folder 18)
  - President's Office: Presidential Search, 1992 - 1993 (Box 93, Folder 19)
  - President's Office: Staff Meetings, 1991 - 1992 (Box 93, Folder 20)
  - President's Office: Wiess House (Trust), 1997 (Box 93, Folder 21)
  - President's Office: Wiess House Renovation, 2000 - 2003 (Box 93, Folder 22)
  - Real Estate, 1997 - 2001 (Box 93, Folder 23)
  - Reliant Energy, 2001 (Box 93, Folder 24)
  - Relocation Allowance Policy, 1993 - 1994 (Box 93, Folder 25)
  - Rental Car Policy, undated (Box 93, Folder 26)
  - Research Accounting, 1990 - 1995 (Box 93, Folder 27)
  - Research Analyst, 1991 - 1998 (Box 93, Folder 28)
  - Research Machine Support Shop, 1993 (Box 93, Folder 29)
  - Residential Colleges Master Plan, 1998 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Rice College, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Rice Della Robbia Tiles, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Rice Trust Inc., 1993 - 2002 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Ryan Lab, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Santa Fe Information Technology Lab, 2000 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Security Access, 1991 - 1995 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Security: Emergency Management Other Plans, 1992 - 1994 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Security: Emergency Management Rice University Plans, 1991 - 1995 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Sources of Revenue, 1998 - 2000 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Student Center/ RMC Fire, 1995 - 2001 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Summary of Legal Agreements Giving Effect to Tuition Plan, 1999 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Tuition I, 1988 - 1998 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Tuition II, 1990 - 1997 (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Tuition Plan Congressional Contact, 1999 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Tuition Plan Correspondence, 1998 - 1999 (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - Tuition Plan Draft Statement of Investment Policies/Objectives, 1999 (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - Tuition Plan Draft Working Plan on Governance, 1999 (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - Tuition Plan Executive Summary, 1999 (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Tuition Plan Quarterly Capital Project Review, 2001 (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - Tuition Plan Consortium Annual Report, June 30, 1999 (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - Tuition Plan Consortium Membership, 2000 (Box 94, Folder 22)
  - Tuition Plan Consortium Nomination Committee, 1998 - 2002 (Box 94, Folder 23)
  - Tuition Plan Consortium Participation Agreement, 1998 (Box 94, Folder 24)
  - Tuition Plan Consortium Summary of Legal Agreements, 2002 (Box 94, Folder 25)
  - Tuition Plan Inc., 1998 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. Articles, 1998 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. Board Meeting, June 9 - 11, 2001 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. Board Meeting, January 30, 2001 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. Board Meeting, February 6, 2000 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. Board Meeting, May 26 - 27, 1999 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. Board Meeting, April 2, 1999 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. Board Meeting, March 21 - 22, 1999 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. Board Meeting, February 1, 1999 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. Board Meeting, April 2, 1998 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. Board Meeting, January 21, 1998 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. Board of Directors, 2000 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. Business Plan, 1987 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. Bylaws, 1998 (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. Consortium Meeting, November 1-2, 1999 (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. Correspondence, 1997 - 1998 (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. Current Organizational Structure, 1998 (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. Denver Presentation, 1998 (Box 95, Folder 18)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. Draft: Proposed Organizational Documents, 1998 (Box 95, Folder 19)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. form 1023, 1998 (Box 95, Folder 20)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. Introduction Business Plan, 1987 - 1998 (Box 95, Folder 21)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. Letters to Legislative Sponsors, 2001 (Box 95, Folder 22)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. Membership Design Issues, 1998 - 1999 (Box 95, Folder 23)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. Notes/Supporting Documentation, 1998 (Box 95, Folder 24)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. Organizational Documents for Meetings, 1998 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. Plan Design Committee, 1998 - 1999 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. Private Letter Ruling Request I, 1998 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. Private Letter Ruling Request II, 1998 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. Private Letter Ruling Request Correspondence, 1998 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. Senate Bill 1133, 1998 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. The Tuition Plan Newsletter, 1999 - 2001 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. TIAA Correspondence, 1998 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. TIAA Meeting, March 19, 1998 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. Tuition Exchange Paper, 1998 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Tuition Remission Survey, 1998 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Tuition Taxpayer's Relief Act, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Tuition Plan Inc. Educate America, undated (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - V W Service Lease Agreements, 1993 - 1996 (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - V W Service Lease Agreements, 1990 - 1992 (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - Buildings: Humanities Building, South New Wiess Colleges, North College Master Planning, 1998 (Box 96, Folder 16)
  - Martel College Under Construction, 2001 (Box 96, Folder 17)
  - Master Planning Presentation for Earl Attwell, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 18)
  - Rice University Utility Infrastructure Report, 2000 (Box 96, Folder 19)
  - Jesse H. Jones Graduate School of Management: New Building, 1999 (Box 96, Folder 20)
  - Pelli Rice University Masterplan Studies (architectural drawings), 1998 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Moore Flood Protection Study, undated (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Stern, Robert A. M. Designs of Jones Graduate School of Management (architectural drawings), 1999 - 2000 (Box 97, Folder 3)
- Series V: Addendum: Neill Binford Finance and Administration, 1938 - 2008
  - Ad Hoc Faculty Advisory Committee on Retirement Report, 1998 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Ad Hoc Security Review Committee Report, 1994-1995 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Computing Subcommittee (1 of 2), 1987-1988 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Administrative Computing Subcommittee (2 of 2), 1987-1989 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Alice Pratt Brown Hall Dedication, 1991 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Architecture Magazines, Articles, and Letters on the Matter (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Art Committee, 2000 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Associate Vice President for Administration Group Policies and Procedures, 1988 - 1993 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Blueprints of Rice University's Buildings (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Board of Control for Rice Institute Cooperative Store (1 of 2), 1938-1966 (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Board of Control for Rice Institute Cooperative Store (2 of 2), 1938-1966 (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Cain Project, 1997-1998 (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Cain Project, 1998-1999 (Box 98, Folder 14)
  - Cain Project - Communication and Personnel Action Forms, 1999-2006 (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - Cain Project, 2000 (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - Cain Project, 2001 - 2002 (Box 98, Folder 17)
  - Cain Project, 2003 - 2004 (Box 98, Folder 18)
  - Cain Project, 2005-2006 (Box 98, Folder 19)
  - Cain Project, 2007-2008 (Box 98, Folder 20)
  - Campaign for Computational Engineering Building (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Campus Food Service Master Plan, 1999 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Campus Store Advisory Committee (1 of 2), 1973-1980 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Campus Store Advisory Committee (2 of 2), 1973 - 1980 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Campus Store Advisory Committee, 1980-1986 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Capital and Major Maintenence Approved Projects (1 of 2), FY 1994 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Capital and Major Maintenence Approved Projects (2 of 2), FY 1994 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Capital Projects (1 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Capital Projects (2 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - CEB - Outram (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - CISE Building, 1992 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Comparative Financial Data Survey, 1989 (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Computer Planning Board and Subcommittees - Final Report, 1990 (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - Construction of Physical Science / Engineering Building, 2006-2010 (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - Continuing Studies Conference Center Project, 2008 (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - Department Chair, Administration Officials, Committees (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - "Diagnostic Purchasing Review" - Project Overview and Phase 1, 1992 (Box 99, Folder 17)
  - Emergency Flood Plan, 1990 (Box 99, Folder 18)
  - Employer Trip Reduction Plan, 1994 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Facilities and Engineering Department Assessment, 1998 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Papers for Inagural Annual Conference of the James A. Baker III Institute for Public Policy, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Salaries Survey, 2004 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Facility Budget Requests (1 of 4), FY 1981-1982 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Facility Budget Requests (2 of 4), FY 1981-1982 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Facility Budget Requests (3 of 4), FY 1981-1982 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Facility Budget Requests (4 of 4), FY 1981-1982 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Facility Budget Requests (1 of 4), FY 1982-1983 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Facility Budget Requests (2 of 4), FY 1982-1983 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Facility Budget Requests (3 of 4), FY 1982-1983 (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - Facility Budget Requests (4 of 4), FY 1982-1983 (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Facility Budget Requests (1 of 4), FY 1983-1984 (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - Facility Budget Requests (2 of 4), FY 1983-1984 (Box 100, Folder 14)
  - Facility Budget Requests (3 of 4), FY 1983-1984 (Box 100, Folder 15)
  - Facility Budget Requests (4 of 4), FY 1983-1984 (Box 100, Folder 16)
  - Facility Budget Requests (1 of 2), FY 1984-1985 (Box 100, Folder 17)
  - Facility Budget Requests (2 of 2), FY 1984-1985 (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - Facility Budget Requests (1 of 2), FY 1985-1986 (Box 100, Folder 19)
  - Facility Budget Requests (2 of 2), FY 1985-1986 (Box 100, Folder 20)
  - Facility Budget Requests (1 of 2), FY 1986-1987 (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - Facility Budget Requests (2 of 2), FY 1986-1987 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Facility Budget Requests (1 of 4), FY 1987-1988 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Facility Budget Requests (2 of 4), FY 1987-1988 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Facility Budget Requests (3 of 4), FY 1987-1988 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Facility Budget Requests (4 of 4), FY 1987-1988 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Facility Budget Requests (1 of 2), FY 1989 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Facility Budget Requests (2 of 2), FY 1989 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Facility Budget Requests, Capital and Major Maintenance (1 of 4), FY 1991-1992 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Facility Budget Requests, Capital and Major Maintenance (2 of 4), FY 1991-1992 (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Facility Budget Requests, Capital and Major Maintenance (3 of 4), FY 1991-1992 (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Facility Budget Requests, Capital and Major Maintenance (4 of 4), FY 1991-1992 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Facility Budget Requests, Capital and Major Maintenance (1 of 4), FY 1993 (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - Facility Budget Requests, Capital and Major Maintenance (2 of 4), FY 1993 (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - Facility Budget Requests, Capital and Major Maintenance (3 of 4), FY 1993 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Facility Budget Requests, Capital and Major Maintenance (4 of 4), FY 1993 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Facility Budget Requests, Capital and Major Maintenance (1 of 4), FY 1994 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Facility Budget Requests, Capital and Major Maintenance (2 of 4), FY 1994 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Facility Budget Requests, Capital and Major Maintenance (3 of 4), FY 1994 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Facility Budget Requests, Capital and Major Maintenance (4 of 4), FY 1994 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - F E Capital / Major Maintenence Review, FY 1994 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Financing Alternatives, 1998 (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - "Flood Prediction Manual for Brays Bayou" Presentation, 1998 (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - "The General Plan of the William M. Rice Institute and its Architectural Development", 1981 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - Implementing "Rice: The Next Century" - Plan, 1997 (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - Landscape Vision and Design Guidelines - Executive Summary, 1990 (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - Letters and Files Concerning the Building for Computational Engineering, 1993 (Box 102, Folder 13)
  - Lighting Study, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 14)
  - Mail Processing and Handling, 1998 (Box 102, Folder 15)
  - Master Plan for Growth, William Marsh Rice University, 1983 (Box 102, Folder 16)
  - New Members of the Buildings and Grounds Committee Orientation, 1996 (Box 102, Folder 17)
  - New Trustees Orientation, 2003 (Box 102, Folder 18)
  - John Outram (1 of 3) (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - John Outram (2 of 3) (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - John Outram (3 of 3) (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - John Outram - Public Praise and Acclaim (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - John Outram Reports and Appendices (1 of 2) (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - John Outram Reports and Appendices (2 of 2) (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Parking Lots (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Parking Protest Letters, FY 1992 - 1993 (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Parking and Traffic (1 of 2), 1992 (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - Parking and Traffic (1 of 2, duplicate), 1992 (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - Parking and Traffic (1 of 2, duplicate), 1992 (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - Parking and Traffic (2 of 2), 1992 (Box 103, Folder 12)
  - Parking and Traffic (2 of 2, duplicate), 1992 (Box 103, Folder 13)
  - Parking and Traffic (2 of 2, duplicate), 1992 (Box 103, Folder 14)
  - Pictures of Board Books, 2004 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Police Training, Rice University, 1996 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Prager, McCarthy, and Sealy Investment Banking Presentation for Rice University, 1998 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - "Preliminary Rating Indicators for Triple AAA Rated Private Universities" - Rating and Financial Analysis, 1998 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Presentation from Dean Currie, 2004 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Project Management and Design Standards Guidelines (1 of 2), 1996 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Project Management and Design Standards Guidelines (2 of 2), 1996 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Renovations for Hamman Hall Proposal, 1990 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - "Rhetoric Across Disciplines" - Presentation, 1988 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Rice Campus Master Plan, 2003 (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Rice Campus Store Ad Hoc Committee Report, 2001 (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Rice Policy Memos (1 of 2), 1993 (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Rice Policy Memos, 1993 (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - Rice University Building and Grounds Book - for Josephine E. Abercrombie (1 of 2), 1994 (Box 104, Folder 14)
  - Rice University Building and Grounds Book - for Josephine E. Abercrombie (2 of 2), 1994 (Box 104, Folder 15)
  - RUPD Plan for Department Evolution, 1991 (Box 104, Folder 16)
  - RUPD Self-Study Report, 1992 (Box 104, Folder 17)
  - SACS - Accredidation, 2006 (Box 104, Folder 18)
  - Space Assessment Final Report, 2002 (Box 104, Folder 19)
  - Space Assignment Committee (1 of 2), 1980-1987 (Box 104, Folder 20)
  - Space Assignment Committee (2 of 2), 1980-1987 (Box 104, Folder 21)
  - Space Inventory (1 of 2), FY 1997 (Box 104, Folder 22)
  - Space Inventory (2 of 2), FY 1997 (Box 104, Folder 23)
  - Space Planning Data, 1998 (Box 104, Folder 24)
  - Space Study - Lou Griffin, 1991 (Box 104, Folder 25)
  - Space Utilization Study by Department (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Space Utilization Study by Department (2 of 2), 1988 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Sports Facility Study, 1991 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Gordon Stanley e-mails and Business Presentations, 1998 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Strategic Plan - Wiess School of Natural Sciences, 1997 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - "Undergraduate Curriculum Revision" - Financial Appeals (1 of 2), 1988-1989 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - "Undergraduate Curriculum Revision" - Financial Appeals (2 of 2), 1988-1989 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - William Marsh Rice Institute Insurance Survey, 1959 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Departmental Operations Microfiche, 1979-1989 (Box 105, Item 1)
  - Electronic Media: 217 - 3" Floppy disks; 3 - VHS; 18 - CD's; 1 - DVD; 1 - Cassette (Box 106)
  - Neill Binford timesheets, Buy/Pay meeting agendas, Y2K Emergency Operations Task Force meeting agendas (Box 106)
  - Fiscal year 1993 financial documents (Box 106)
  - Crisis management documents (Box 106)
  - September 1994 Campus Security Act (Box 106)
  - Safety and security documents (Box 106)
  - Salary proposal table (Box 106)
  - Dean Currie personnel files (Box 106)
  - Printing Center closing documents (Box 106)
  - Campus crimes tables (Box 106)
  - Rice crime data charts (Box 106)
  - RUPD dispatch calls, criminal suspects tables (Box 106)
  - Parking/bus financial information (Box 106)
  - Division 6 budgeting, fiscal year 1993 (Box 106)
  - Dean Currie letter templates (Box 106)
  - Individual salary comparisons (Box 106)
  - Rice campus store financial records, fiscal year 1997; job descriptions (Box 106)
  - Unidentified financial document (Box 106)
  - Office of Finance and Administration records home page (Box 106)
  - Div6 Dir_Mgr salariesFY99.csv (Box 106)
  - RUPD budget documents (Box 106)
  - Fiscal year 1995 budget data (Box 106)
  - Fall 1996 textbook master list (Box 106)
  - Fiscal year 1997 budgeting documents (Box 106)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee meeting minutes (Box 106)
  - Capital & Major Maintenance Program budget, fiscal year 1997 (Box 106)
  - Advisory Committee on Purchasing and Receiving documents (Box 106)
  - 1989 Rice University phone book, related documents (Box 106)
  - Capital & Major Maintenance Program budget, fiscal year 1993 (Box 106)
  - Capital & Major Maintenance Program budget, fiscal year 1992 (Box 106)
  - "A 50 Year Master Plan for the Institutions of the Texas Medical Center" (1999) and Master Plan Progress Report (2000), 1999-2000 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - "A Preliminary Proposal for Landscape Improvements for 1990 Economic Summit for Rice University" (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Alterations to Biology, Geology, and Space Science Technology Labs, 1996 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Chemistry/Nanotechnology Building, Predeck Rendition, 1995 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Computational Engineering Building, Design (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Computational Engineering Building, Chemistry-Nanotechnology Building, Baker Institute Building, Designs, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Founders' Court Garage, Cannady Studio, 2001 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Hermann Drive Relief Storm Sewer Project, 2005 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Humanities Building, Rice University, 1999 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - James A. Baker III Institute for Public Policy Fountain Study, 1997 (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - James A. Baker III Institute for Public Policy Sketches, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Jones Graduate School of Management Conceptual and Schematic Designs, 1999 (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Martel College, Masterplan and Schematic Drawings, 1999 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Masterplan for Rice University, 1994 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Masterplan for Rice University, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Masterplan for Rice University, 1999 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Masterplan for Rice University, 2002 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Masterplan Study Draft for Rice University, 2004 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - New Projects Construction, 1999 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Parking Study, Rice University, 1991 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Pelli, Fondren Library Plans, 1999 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Possible Improvements, 2001-2002 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Proposed Exterior Signage Program for Rice University, 1991 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Reckling Park at Rice University, Plans, 1998-1999 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Rice Book Store, Concept Sketch Pak, 1998 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Rice Employees Metro Map (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Rice University Flood Prevention Study (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Rice University, North Campus Masterplan, 1999 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Signage and Wayfinding Design Intent / Bid Document, 2005 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Sign Design (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Site Plan for the Shepherd School of Music (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - South College Project Drawings (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Rice Stadium security information (Box 106)
- Series VI: Oversize Materials
  - Ralph S. O'Connor House, 2006 (Map-drawer 148, Item 5)
  - Computational Engineering Building (Duncan Hall) floor plans Project number 9339 (4 sets), 1994-1995 (Map-drawer 148, Item 5a)
- Series VII: Addendum: Neill Binford, Assoc. VP for Finance & Admin.
  - Briefing paper for Rice Univ. President-elect David Leebron, 2004-01 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - KTRU North Park annual tower inspection report, 2004-04-02 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Ad hoc Security Review Cmte. report, 1994-95 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Collegiate Licensing Co. sweatshop issue, 2001 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Student Association, 1990s (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Transportation, 1990s (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Parking Cmte., 2000 (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Departmental operations fiche, 1990-1993 (Box 110)
  - Campus Police Dept.
    - Issues, 1998 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Special events, non-Rice, 1990s (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Sexual assault, 1990s (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Alcohol and drugs, 1990s (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Bomb threats, 1990s (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Policies and procedures, 1990s-2000s (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Racial solidarity rallly, 2000-04 (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Profiling, 2002-2003 (Box 111, Folder 8)
- Series VIII: Addendum: Dean Currie Finance and Administration
  - Administration (General)
    - F&A Correspondence, 1991-2003 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Administrative Computing (Banner), 1990-1992 (1 of 3) (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Administrative Computing (Banner), 1990-1992 (2 of 3) (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Administrative Computing (Banner), 1990-1992 (3 of 3) (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Berlin Wall Section, 1989-2001 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Budget Planning: Training, Software, 1991-1995 (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Campus Landscape Proposal, 1990 (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Campus Security, 1988-1997 (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - Campus Security News, Articles, 1994-1997 (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Classroom Study, 1995-1998 (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - Electronic Studio, 1994 (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - Environmental Health and Safety, 1992-2003 (Box 112, Folder 12)
    - Martin Luther King Day, 1992-1996 (Box 112, Folder 14)
    - Parking, 1989-1991 (Box 112, Folder 15)
    - Parking, 1992-1999 (Box 112, Folder 16)
    - Parking, 2000-2002 (Box 112, Folder 17)
    - Parking Community Issues, 1997-2001 (Box 112, Folder 18)
    - Rice Village Traffic Study, 1993 (Box 112, Folder 19)
    - Space Planning, 1999 (Box 112, Folder 20)